I'm done with you.
（流子(りゅうこ)）もう うんざりだ
二度とお前は着ない
I'm never putting you on again.
（鮮血(せんけつ)）流子…
Ryuuko!
Just looking at you pisses me off!
（流子）
お前を見てるとムカつくんだよ
同(おんな)じ化け物(もん)だからな
'Cause we're both the
same breed of monster!
That's right! I'm not human!
ああそうだ 私は人間じゃない！
I'm a Life Fiber monster!
生命戦維(せんい)の化け物だ！
That's not right, Ryuuko!
（マコ）おかしいよ流子ちゃん
Isn't Senketsu your friend?
鮮血ちゃんは流子ちゃんの
友達でしょ
そんな態度 いつもの
流子ちゃんじゃないよ！
This isn't like you at all!
At all!
（マイク:マコ）
ないよ ないよ ないよ…
At all!
This isn't like you at all!
いつもの流子ちゃんじゃないよ
At all! At all! At all! At all!
じゃないよ じゃないよ
じゃないよ じゃないよ！
Well, yeah. I'm not my usual self.
いつもの あたしじゃないんだよ
Turns out my whole life
until now was a lie,
（流子）今までのは全部
ウソっぱちだったんだ
and I'm actually a monster.
Not a human.
I'm some unkillable freak,
just like Ragyou.
...No...
Hmm. You're looking
awfully grumpy today, Ryuuko.
Harime Nui!
EPISODE 20
FAR FROM THE MADDENING CROWDS
unmei no ito wo tachikitta sono saki ni
It all begins when we sever the threads of fate
senobi shiteitanda
I was trying to be someone I'm not
あたしは化け物だ
senobi shiteitanda
I was trying to be someone I'm not
ただの人間じゃない
羅暁(らぎょう)と同じ殺されても死なない—
senobi shiteitanda
I was trying to be someone I'm not
kutsuzure darake no
In a cramped world
化け物なんだ
semai sekai de
With no breathing room
そんな…
semai sekai de
With no breathing room
runway wo aruku
As I walked down my runway
（縫(ぬい)）ん〜
runway wo aruku
As I walked down my runway
（縫）
ご機嫌斜めだね 流子ちゃん
runway wo aruku
As I walked down my runway
egao no uragawa
I thought I'd concealed it
（流子）針目(はりめ)縫！
egao no uragawa
I thought I'd concealed it
kakushita tsumori de
Behind the smile that masked my face
ウフッ
kakushita tsumori de
Behind the smile that masked my face
dakedo itsumo kimi ni wa
But it doesn't work on you
minukarete shimatte ite
You always see through my facade
konna no wa hajimete de
Nobody's ever unraveled me like this before
tomadou kedo
I don't know what to do
hoka no dare ni mo kikonasenai
Nobody else can pull these outfits off
nandaka wakannai
A somewhat ambiguous fever
atsusa ga mune wo kogasu kara
Threatens to burn our hearts away
unmei no ito taguriyoseta sono saki ni
It all begins once we rein in the threads of fate
ima atarashii yoake ga kuru
A new day will dawn for us
omoi wa kitto hitotsu
We must be one in spirit
ウフフフッ でも—
But I think you're getting mad
at the wrong person.
怒る相手が
違うんじゃないのかな
I seem to remember you
wanting to avenge your father.
（縫）流子ちゃんは お父様の敵(かたき)を
取りたいんじゃなかったっけ
その敵の僕を無視して—
And yet you're ignoring me, his killer,
こんなゴミかすどもを
相手にしてるんじゃ—
and playing with a
bunch of weaklings instead.
You're making me sad!
縫 さ〜み〜し〜い〜
Screw you!
（流子）なめんな！
（縫）ひ〜い
That's the spirit, daughter of mine!
（羅暁）そのとおりだよ 我が娘よ
Don't call me your daughter!
娘じゃねえ！
I can understand your turmoil.
（羅暁）戸惑うのも無理はない
Kiryuuin Souichirou—no, I suppose
I should call him "Matoi Isshin" instead.
鬼龍院装一郎(きりゅういんそういちろう)… いや 纏一身(まといいっしん)か
This was a dastardly scheme
concocted by that foolish man.
全ては あの愚かしい男が仕組んだ
卑劣な計画だ
He treated his own daughter
as but a mere tool.
自分の娘を道具としてしか扱わない
As your mother, I understand
your rage so much it hurts.
この母には お前の怒り
痛いほどわか…
Enough of your barefaced tripe!
（流子）何 したり顔で
能書き垂れてんだよ！
Marvelous. Your unyielding
spirit is a sight to behold.
すばらしい そのまっすぐな気迫
Watching you excites me far more
than that worthless firstborn of mine!
お前を見ているほうが—
出来損ないの長女よりも
よほど心が躍る！
You wretch!
（蟇郡(がまごおり)）貴様！
皐月(さつき)様をバカにすると許さんぞ！
Don't you dare insult Lady Satsuki!
What exactly do I owe a girl who
stabbed her own mother in the back?
（羅暁）実の母を背中から
串刺しにするような娘に—
何の義がある
Do you hate your mother?
憎むか この母を
Do you resent me, Ragyou?
恨むか この羅暁を
ぶち殺してやる
I'm gonna kick your ass all the way to Hell.
（羅暁）フフッ ならば来い！
Then come to me!
本能字(ほんのうじ)学園を我ら親子の
決着の場としようぞ
Honnouji Academy shall be the stage where you and I,
mother and daughter, settle things once and for all!
Fine by me.
（流子）
上等だ その首 洗って待ってろ
I'm coming for your head.
楽しみ！ アデュー モナミ
I can't wait.
Adieu, mon amie!
Wait, Ryuuko!
（美木杉(みきすぎ)）待て 流子君
Don't try to stop me.
止めんな
This is a trap.
（美木杉）これはワナだ
怒りに任せて乗り込むのは危険だ
Barging in in a fit of rage
would put you in too much danger.
Quit acting like you're
my goddamn teacher!
いつまでも先公面してんじゃねえ！
This is all your fault in the first place.
もともと てめえのせいだろうが
You played dumb,
despite knowing everything.
全部知ってて涼しい顔して—
Deep down, I bet you were
laughing at this freak of a girl!
腹ん中じゃ化け物娘と
せせら笑ってたんだろう！
そんなことはない
Of course not.
（流子）やかましい
てめえの言い訳は聞き飽きた！
Shut up.
I've had enough of your excuses!
Looks like humans and clothing
really can't see eye to eye.
（黄長瀬(きながせ)）やはり服と人間が
わかり合えるのは無理なようだな
The hell are you talking about?
何をまぬけたことを言ってる
I've never been human to begin with!
こっちは はなから
人間じゃねえんだよ
Step aside!
どけ！ 邪魔するヤツは
誰だろうと ぶっ潰す！
I'll crush anyone who gets in my way!
あ… 一撃でビルを…
She felled two buildings with one strike?
What terrifying fury.
（猿投山(さなげやま)）すさまじい殺気だ
Ryuuko.
（鮮血）流子…
See that? That's who I am right now.
そう これが今の私だ！
てめえらは極(ごく)制服を脱げばいい
All you guys have to do is
cast off your Ultima Uniforms.
だけど あたしは死ぬまでずっと
生命戦維と一緒なんだ
But I'm gonna have to live
with Life Fibers until I die!
Senketsu wasn't the weapon
created to kill his brethren!
仲間殺しのためにつくられた
戦闘兵器は鮮血じゃねえ！
この あたしだったんだ
It was me!
...No...
（鮮血）そんな…
（流子）
てめえ見てると いらつくんだよ
Just looking at you pisses me off!
You remind me of my own stupidity!
自分のまぬけさにな！
...Ryuuko...
（鮮血）流子…
If you got that, then don't
come clinging to me again.
（流子）わかったら
二度とまとわりつくんじゃねえ
Oh, but he will!
まとわりつくよ！
だって鮮血ちゃんは
流子ちゃんの一張羅の親友だもん
I mean, Senketsu's both your
best outfit and your best friend!
いつまでも いつまでも—
He'll cling to you forever and ever, like an outfit charged with static electricity!
静電気がいっぱいの洋服みたいに
まとわりつくよ！
Whoa!
バチッ！
I felt a spark run through my body!
あ！ バチッときた あ…
Ryuuko?
流子ちゃん…
...Ryuuko...
流子君…
There are no signs of
any COVERS reinforcements.
（犬牟田(いぬむた)）
カバーズの援軍は見当たらないね
So they were after
Matoi Ryuuko, and her alone?
（黄長瀬）ヤツらの狙いは
纏流子だけってことか
If only I'd realized the truth
...about Ryuuko earlier...
（美木杉）流子君の正体に
僕がもっと早く気付いていれば…
（蛇崩(じゃくずれ)）何かできた？
それは思い上がりよ
..."I could've done something"?...
Talk about conceited.
We can't count on Matoi Ryuuko
to fight for us anymore.
纏流子という戦力は失った
The only thing we should be thinking
about is what we can do right now.
その上で我々に何ができるか—
今 考えるのはそれだけだ
There's no time for regrets.
後悔をしている暇はない
（美木杉）
君たち腹が据わってるね
高校生なのに
For high schoolers, you guys sure
have good heads on your shoulders.
Lady Satsuki did train us well, you know.
皐月様に鍛えられたもの
この程度でヘコんでるわけには
いかないの
We can't sit here moping
over something like this.
（犬牟田）纏を挑発して—
What exactly do they plan to achieve by provoking
Matoi Ryuuko into storming Honnouji Academy?
本能字学園に呼び寄せて
何を狙うのか…
If she takes out Ragyou and Harime Nui,
that would save us a lot of trouble.
あいつが羅暁と針目縫を
倒してくれれば面倒が省けるが…
This is the Kiryuuin Ragyou we're
talking about. It won't be that easy.
相手は鬼龍院羅暁だ
そう簡単にいくわけがない
（鮮血）流子は泣いていたよ
Ryuuko was crying.
Filled with suffering and resentment,
苦しんで 恨んで 今度はあいつが
苦い涙を流していた
it was she who was
shedding bitter tears this time.
I shall head for Honnouji Academy.
私は本能字学園に向かう
流子を放ってはおけない
I can't leave Ryuuko on her own!
That said, I'm sure my words
won't reach anyone.
と言っても
誰にも伝わらないだろうが
（マコ）
鮮血ちゃん 流子ちゃんを
追いかけたいのね
Senketsu, you want to
go after Ryuuko, right?
（鮮血）え？
（マコ）追いかけたいのね
You want to go after her, right?
（鮮血）あっ ああ…
わかるのか 私の言葉が
Y-Yes. You can understand
what I'm saying?
（マコ）わあ！
わかったわかった よしよし
All right, I get it.
There, there.
（美木杉）満艦飾(まんかんしょく)君
鮮血の言葉が聞こえるのかい？
Mankanshoku!
Can you hear Senketsu's voice?
（マコ）全然！
（鮮血）やっぱり…
Not at all.
Figures.
But I can understand how he feels.
でも気持ちならわかります
だって私も同じ気持ちだもん！
After all, I feel the same way.
Uh... I think we're all going to
want to go after Matoi Ryuuko now.
（犬牟田）ああ たぶん みんなも
纏流子の後を追いたくなると思うよ
What do you mean?
（蟇郡）どういうことだ
（犬牟田）ようやく
学園のシステムに入り込めた
I finally managed to infiltrate
the academy's system.
They seem to be building something.
（黄長瀬）何か作ってるな
（犬牟田）それも気になるが
今のポイントはこれ
That bothers me too, but there are
more pressing concerns right now.
Lady Satsuki!
（蟇郡）皐月様！
Lady Satsuki, you say?
（猿投山）皐月様だと？
生きているのか！
Is she alive?
How cruel.
（蛇崩）ひどい
貴様ら見るな 見てはいかん！
Don't look, you fiends!
You must not lay eyes on this!
My Mind's Eye doesn't work on screens!
Someone tell me what's going on!
（猿投山）
俺の心眼通(しんがんつう)も画面には効かんのだ
誰か教えてくれ！
（美木杉）
鎖でつるされてるよ 素っ裸で
She's hanging by chains.
Stark naked, too.
Chains? Stark naked?!
（猿投山）鎖で素っ裸だと？
どういうことだ！
What's the meaning of this?!
（蟇郡）どういうことでもない！
Nothing!
Settle down, would you?
（犬牟田）ちょっと騒がないで
問題はここからだから
We haven't gotten to the real issue yet.
音量 上げるよ
I'm raising the volume.
...She's sharpening...
研いでいる 皐月様が反逆の牙を
Lady Satsuki's sharpening
the fangs of rebellion!
（犬牟田）正確には爪だけど
Nails, to be more precise.
（犬牟田たち）フッ
（蛇崩）アハッ
Milady!
（揃(そろい)）お嬢様
（マコ）ああ…
（蛇崩）まったく
オタクは回りくどいわね
Sheesh. How roundabout can she be?
If she was alive, then she
should've just said so already.
生きてるんなら生きてるって
さっさと言えばいいじゃない
確かに 我々も
向かうべき場所が決まったな
Yeah. Looks like we know where to go.
Indeed.
（猿投山）
ああ 狙いは皐月様の奪還
Our goal is to rescue Lady Satsuki!
The enemy awaits at Honnouji!
“敵は本能字にあり”だ！
Oh man. He went and said it.
（犬牟田）あ〜あ 言っちゃった
みんな我慢してたのに
And here we were
all trying to hold it in.
Man, that sorta stuff is
seriously embarrassing, you know?
（蛇崩）もう 一緒に動く
私たちまで恥ずかしいでしょ
これだから北関東のボケ猿は
デリカシーがないのよ
This is why I can't stand dumb monkeys
from Northern Kanto. No tact at all!
Oh dear.
まいったな 君たちがそれだけ
やる気満々だと—
If you guys are so up for it,
I'll have to take off my underwear too.
僕もパンツを脱がざるをえないな
Don't you dare, pervert.
（蛇崩）やめてよ変態
So long as we can't rely on Ryuuko,
流子君が当てにできない以上
人類の勝利は
鬼龍院皐月なくしてありえない
mankind cannot prevail
without Kiryuuin Satsuki.
Nudist Beach shall offer up all of its
manpower to Operation Rescue Satsuki.
ヌーディスト･ビーチの持てる
戦力の全てを—
皐月奪還作戦に注ごう
Wait, are you going to use the Naked Sun?!
（黄長瀬）
おい まさか“裸の太陽”を！
（マコ）“裸の”？
Naked?
That's right! We're all set to go.
ああ 準備はできている
Behold!
見たまえ これが僕たちの
最後の１枚だ！
This is our very last piece!
The S.S. Naked Sun!
裸の太陽丸 出航！
Set sail!
All hands, get ready to sail!
総員 出航準備だ！
Have all non-combatants
disembark the ship!
戦闘員以外
至急 船から退出させろ！
All right! It's about freakin' time!
（宝多(たからだ)）よっしゃあ いよいよや！
Go break a leg, you guys.
（宝多）お前ら しっかり気張れよ
道頓堀(どうとんぼり)ゲート オープンや！
Open the Doutonbori Gate!
Opening the Doutonbori Gate!
（スピーカー:男性）
道頓堀 ゲート オープン
Opening the Doutonbori Gate!
クイックリー クイックリー
Quick!
The underground base was a ship?
（蟇郡）
地下基地は船だったのか
It took every last penny of the
Takarada Conglomerate to finish this,
（美木杉）宝多財閥の金を
根こそぎ搾り上げて完成させた—
ヌーディスト･ビーチ最後の切り札
Nudist Beach's final trump card:
The S.S. Naked Sun!
裸の太陽丸！
S.S. NAKED SUN
Mako!
（薔薇蔵(ばらぞう)）マコ！
Oh, Dad! Mom!
わあっ 父ちゃん 母ちゃん！
...You guys...
（美木杉）あんたたち…
We're coming with you!
俺たちも行くぞ
（薔薇蔵）
医者が乗っておいたほうが
都合がいいだろう
It'd help you to have a doctor on board.
BACK-ALLEY MEDICAL CORPS
THE MANKANSHOKU FAMILY
（好代(すくよ)）本能町(ほんのうちょう)には
我が家があります
Honnou Town is our hometown, after all,
and I've been wanting
to pick up some frying oil.
ちょうど揚げ物の油が
欲しかったんです
Plus, this seems like fun.
（又郎(またろう)）面白そうだしな
（ガッツ）ガッツ ガッツ！
Guts, guts!
うん 行こう みんなで！
Yup! Let's go together!
Now hang on just a second.
いやいやいや そもそも
劣等生 連れてくとは言ってないし
We never said anything about taking
the underachiever along to begin with.
Give it up, Jakuzure.
無駄だ 蛇崩
Mankanshoku's the most
stubborn person in Honnouji.
満艦飾の聞く耳の持たなさは
本能字一
Not even you can pull out the earplugs
she wears, for they are earplugs of the heart.
いくらお前でもこいつの心の耳栓を
抜くことはできん
Uh, I'm not sure I follow.
（蛇崩）
よくわかんないんですけど
Well, too late for that now.
（美木杉）
まあ しかたないでしょう
船は出ちゃったし
The ship has sailed.
I got a lotta money ridin' on that thing!
（宝多）
大枚つぎ込んだんや
Go give 'em threaded freaks
a beatin' they'll never forget!
布っきれの化け物どもに
がつんといてこましたれや！
I'm countin' on ya.
頼むで
（流子）お〜ら〜！
Ragyou!
羅暁！ 縫！ どこだ
Nui!
Where are you?!
約束どおり 来てやったぞ！
I've come, just as I said I would!
（縫）う〜ん すてき すてき！
Amazing!
You're just so wild
and cool today, Ryuuko!
今日の流子ちゃんはワイルドで
一段とかっこいいわ！
Spare me the small talk.
（流子）
御託はいい てめえと羅暁を
ぶっ殺しに来たんだからな
I'm here to kill you and Ragyou.
And what will that achieve?
（縫）僕と羅暁様を殺して
どうするの？
You can no longer go back to
the life you used to have, you know.
もう昔の生活には戻れないんだよ
だから御託はいいんだよ
Like I said, spare me the small talk.
（縫）フン
Hup!
（縫）はい！
（流子）フン！
（縫）アッハハハ
Wow, so fast!
速い 速い 速い 速ーい！
So it begins.
始まったか
Have some more!
もう一丁！
Missile confirmed to have hit target.
（犬牟田）
ミサイル ターゲットに命中を確認
How easy it'd be if
this was enough to kill her.
これでやられるようなヤツなら
楽なんだけどね
Sure, we may have seen it coming,
（犬牟田）予想してたとはいえ—
but it's really annoying to
see her act like it was nothing.
あそこまで平然とされると
ムカつくな
フッ 醜い鋼鉄の塊が…
What an ugly lump of steel.
I'll let you have all the
fun you want for now.
今は好きなだけ はしゃいでいろ
派手な迎えだな
What a flashy ride.
My fake toenail's made from
the same material as Bakuzan.
縛斬(ばくざん)と同じ材質の付け爪だ
貴様ら布きれ相手には十分だろ
It should be more than enough
for you scraps of cloth.
I get it, Ryuuko.
（縫）わかるよ 流子ちゃん
さみしいんだよね
You're lonely, aren't you?
自分が人間だと信じてたのに—
You believed you were human,
敵だと思ってた生命戦維が
自分を生かしてくれていた
but you were being kept alive by the
same Life Fibers you considered your enemy.
In that case,
who exactly are your allies?
じゃあ 自分の味方は誰？
Who exactly are your enemies?
自分の敵は誰？
There's no human out there
who can understand you.
誰も自分を
わかってくれる人間はいない
Quit running your mouth and fight me!
（流子）戦ってるのに
ぐだぐだしゃべんじゃねえ！
But you know what, Ryuuko?
（縫）でもね 流子ちゃん
絶望しちゃいけない
You mustn't despair!
You still have me!
君には僕がいる
僕だけが流子ちゃんを
わかってあげられるんだよ
I'm the only one
who can understand you!
ハッ 好きなだけほざけ！
Say what you want!
But save the rest
for when you're in Hell!
続きは地獄でな！
（縫）キャー！
Just kidding!
なーんてね
Lookie, look! This is my heart.
見て見て 僕の心臓
Just watch it pulsate
and sparkle with Life Fibers.
生命戦維の輝きが脈打って
ホントにきれいだよね
Isn't it oh-so-pretty?
（流子）てめえ…
（縫）そう 僕も君と同じ
...Are you...
Yup.
I'm just like you.
The only difference between us
１つ違うとすれば 君は羅暁様の
おなかの中で育ったけど—
is that you grew within
Lady Ragyou's belly,
whereas I grew within an
artificial womb made of Life Fibers.
僕は生命戦維で出来た子宮の中で
育ったってことかな
だから僕は君の魂の姉妹(きょうだい)なんだ
That makes the two of us soul sisters.
Screw that!
ふざけんな 勝手にどんどん
姉妹 増やすんじゃねえ！
My family's big enough already!
But you can't go against
the threads of fate!
でも運命の糸には逆らえない
Shut your mouth!
やかましい！ う…
...That's...
あれは…
Junketsu!
純潔！ 何？
What?!
（羅暁）グランクチュリエから
心を込めたプレゼントだよ
This is a heartfelt gift
from the Grand Couturier.
Ragyou, you bitch!
羅暁 てめえ 糸だと…
When did these threads get here?
いつの間に…
While we were fighting, I stuck these
Marionette Threads in you for her.
（縫）戦っている間に採寸して
しつけ針を打たせてもらったの
You're my precious daughter.
（羅暁）お前はかわいい私の娘だ
I can't have you wearing a
cheap outfit like that Senketsu.
鮮血などという半端な服を
着てはいけない
If you're going to wear clothes,
you should make them the very best.
着るのなら一流の服を着なさい
やめろ！ ああ…
Stop it!
（羅暁）神衣(かむい)純潔
Godrobe Junketsu!
それこそが お前にふさわしい
That is the garment that best suits you.
（皐月）あれは純潔
Is that Junketsu?
Matoi?
纏… そういうことか
So that is what's happening.
今の私には止めるすべがない
I have no means to
stop them right now.
くっ 大量生産の安物どもが！
Damn mass-produced trash.
（蟇郡）ていや！
Jump!
（猿投山）フッ
（蟇郡）フン
（蛇崩）アハッ
Lady Satsuki!
（猿投山）皐月様
（蛇崩）お風邪を召します これを
Let us help. Here.
Sorry we're late.
（蟇郡）
お迎え遅くなりました
Don't be. You Four Devas always
show up at the perfect time.
（皐月）いや さすが四天王
いいタイミングだ
（羅暁）
純潔に心を委ねなさい 流子
Entrust your heart
to Junketsu, Ryuuko.
Knock it off!
やめろ…
Stop!
やめろ〜！
（羅暁）そう それがお前の幸せ
...Yes. That is your happiness—
服に着られることの幸福
the good fortune of being worn by clothing.
You understand, don't you, Ryuuko?
わかるね 流子
Yes, Mother!
はい お母様！
なるほど
ヌーディスト･ビーチの旗艦か
I see.
Nudist Beach's flagship, huh?
Come to think of it, the Takarada
Conglomerate did begin as a shipyard.
そういえば宝多財閥の発端は
造船だったな
Right this way, Lady Satsuki.
さあ 皐月様こちらへ
（揃）お嬢様 むさ苦しい所ですが
Milady.
While this may be
...too filthy a place for you...
（皐月）
お前のお茶を飲めるだけでも
戻ってきたかいはある 揃
Just being able to drink your tea
makes coming back worth it, Soroi.
あなたの奪還に成功した以上
Now that we've successfully rescued you,
it wouldn't be safe to
stick around in this area.
この辺りに
とどまっているのは危険だ
Shall we head back to Osaka for now?
いったん大阪に戻りますか？
I doubt we'll be able to.
それは かなわぬだろうな
Soon, we'll have to face
our worst possible enemy.
我々はすぐに最悪の敵を
相手にすることになる
Bad news.
（犬牟田）ヤバい 何か高速で
この船に突っ込んでくるぞ
Something's heading
straight for this ship, and fast.
（美木杉）何？
What?!
I'm gonna destroy it all!
ぶっ壊してやるよ
Every last thing!
何もかもな！
Yeah, this certainly is
the worst case scenario.
（美木杉）確かに最悪の事態だ
Things aren't looking good.
（犬牟田）
マズいな このままだとこの船
女子高生１人に沈められるよ
Unless we do something, this ship
will be sunk by a lone high school girl.
アッハハハ！
That idiot!
（黄長瀬）あのバカ！
（美木杉）紬(つむぐ)！
Tsumugu!
死ぬぞ
You'll die, you know.
（黄長瀬）
俺専用のＤＴＲ試作機がある
I'll use that secret DTR
that was personalized for me.
...But that's still not...
しかし あれはまだ…
あんたのより装甲を強化したやつだ
やってみる価値はある
It's got stronger armor than yours.
It's worth a shot!
トゥ！
（蛇崩）皐月様 これを
Here, Lady Satsuki.
They're better off in
your hands than in ours.
我々が持つよりも
あなたが持つほうがふさわしい
What?!
（マコ）え〜 なんで
流子ちゃんが純潔 着てるの？
Why's Ryuuko wearing Junketsu?
This can't be!
（鮮血）バカな
流子が私以外の神衣を…
How could Ryuuko
wear another Godrobe?
（皐月）入るぞ
（マコ）ん？
I'm coming in.
Lady Satsuki!
（マコ）皐月様！
（黄長瀬）うっ う… ぐわ！
Oh, look. It's a guy with a mohawk riding a mech
that exposes his ass to the entire world.
（流子）相変わらず 尻丸出しの
メカに乗ったモヒカン野郎が
死にな
Die.
Wow.
（流子）へえ〜 そうくるか
So that's your game.
...The two of you...
お前たち２人が—
joined hands, eh?
手を組んだわけだ
Hate me as you may,
（皐月）私が憎いかもしれない
それでも今のあいつを
止められるのは私とお前だけだ
you and I are the only ones
who can stop her right now.
Please lend me your strength,
お前の力を貸してくれ 鮮血
Senketsu!
kurikaesu mainichi ga
My monotonous everyday life
totsuzen iro wo kaeru
Took on a new hue
sonna koto dokka nozonde itanda kedo ne
A part of me always wished for that to happen
iza to naru to
But when it actually did
okubyoumono deshita
I was too scared to act
himitsu ne
That's a secret, okay?
hitori furuete
Trembling alone
soshite kimi ni aitakute
I miss you so much
zutto mikata da yo nante ieta nara
If only I could tell you that I'll always be on your side
muteki
We could be invincible
sou sa tobitatsu toki wa futari de
When we take flight, we'll do so together
tachimukai
We'll make a stand
kakaekirenai okubyou ni
I want to keep smiling
tsuppattatte waratte itai
Even when my cowardice freezes me in place
hitori kiri zutsu ga awasatte
Every little thing will come together
ookina chikara ni naru yo
To give us great strength
ima nee kanjita
That's how I feel right now
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
（鮮血）
着たい服と着られない服
２つの違いは何なのか
Clothing you want to wear,
and clothing you cannot wear.
CANNOT WEAR
What is the difference
between the two?
流子と皐月
ねじれにねじれた２人の姉妹
RYUUKO AND SATSUKI
Ryuuko and Satsuki,
two twisted sisters!
TWO SISTERS
The time has come at last to
unravel the tangled threads of fate!
もつれっぱなしの因果の糸を
いよいよ ほどく時が来た
AT LAST
次回 キルラキル
「未完成」
Next time on KILL la KILL, "Incomplete"!
EPISODE 21 INCOMPLETE